Chip Py Go-Go Collection 199
People's Archive, MLK Library
- Series 1: Photographs, 2011-2020; 199chippy
  - Ant, Kacey Williams, and Bo Beedy perform with BLACK ALLEY at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-09-04; 199chippy_1899; Ant plays electric guitar, Kacey Williams holds a microphone in her right hand, and Bo Beedy plays the congas, bongos, cymbal, and cowbell while performing with BLACK ALLEY at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Kacey Williams and Bo Beedy perform with BLACK ALLEY at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-09-04; 199chippy_1900; Kacey Williams holds a microphone in her right hand and sings and Bo Beedy plays the congas, bongos, and cowbell with BLACK ALLEY at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Kacey Williams and Bo Beedy perform with BLACK ALLEY at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-09-04; 199chippy_1901; Kacey Williams holds a microphone in her right hand and sings and Bo Beedy plays the congas, bongos, and cowbell with BLACK ALLEY at Ivy City Smokehouse. To the right an electric guitarist is visible.
  - Kacey Williams and Bo Beedy perform with BLACK ALLEY at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-09-04; 199chippy_1902; Kacey Williams holds a microphone in her right hand and sings and Bo Beedy plays the congas, bongos, and cowbell with BLACK ALLEY at Ivy City Smokehouse. To the right an electric guitarist is visible.
  - Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performs with Chuck Brown Band at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-09-04; 199chippy_1903; Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go plays electric guitar while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - The Kim Michelle Experience performs at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-10-07; 199chippy_1957; Ms Kim and KeKe perform with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Hope Udobi, KeKe, and Ms Kim perform with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-10-07; 199chippy_1958; Hope Udobi plays the keys while KeKe and Ms Kim sing during a performance with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Hope Udobi, KeKe, and Ms Kim perform with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-10-07; 199chippy_1959; Hope Udobi plays the keys while KeKe and Ms Kim sing during a performance with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Hope Udobi, KeKe, and Ms Kim perform with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-10-07; 199chippy_1960; Hope Udobi plays the keys while KeKe and Ms Kim sing during a performance with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Hope Udobi, KeKe, and Ms Kim perform with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-10-07; 199chippy_1961; Hope Udobi plays the keys while KeKe and Ms Kim sing during a performance with The Kim Michelle Experience at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Trombone King, Rafael Gerald, and Jeremiah Boulware perform with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2017-10-07; 199chippy_1962; Trombone King holds a trombone and smiles back at drummer Rafael Gerald while Jeremiah Boulware plays electric guitar during a performance with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - KK arrives to perform with Chuck Brown Band for performance at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1904; KK arrives to perform with Chuck Brown Band for performance at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Chuck Brown Band performs at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1905; Chuck Brown Band performs at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Animal and Mighty Moe perform with Chuck Brown Band at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1906; Animal plays the drum set and Mighty Moe plays the congas while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Animal and Mighty Moe perform with Chuck Brown Band at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1907; Animal plays the drum set and Mighty Moe plays the congas while performing with Chuck Brown Band at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Ms Kim and DJ Blakberri visit KK backstage at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1908; Ms Kim and DJ Blakberri visit with KK backstage at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Fan plays tambourine while Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performs with Chuck Brown Band for performance at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1909; Fan plays tambourine while Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go performs with Chuck Brown Band for performance at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Ms Kim and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go perform with Chuck Brown Band at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1910; Ms Kim and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go on electric guitar perform with Chuck Brown Band at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Fan shows off their Chuck Brown shoes, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1911; Fan shows off their shoes with a custom painting of Chuck Brown during a performance of Chuck Brown Band.
  - Chuck Brown Band performs for a performance at Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1912; Chuck Brown Band performs for performance at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Fans shows Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go their Chuck Brown shoes, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1913; Fan shows Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go their shoes with a custom painted portrait of Chuck Brown during a Chuck Brown Band performance at Pearl Street Warehouse.
  - Backstage at the Pearl Street Warehouse, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1914; Tom Goldfogle, Chuck Brown's former manager, snaps a photo of KK and Frank 'Scooby' Sirius: the Godson of Go-Go in the backroom of the Pearl Street Warehouse. KK rests her head on Scooby's shoulder. Brad Clements looks on. Another band member stands in the corner.
  - 2017 Chuck Brown Day parking directions, 2017-11-23; 199chippy_1915; A person holds an arrow shaped sign that reads 'Chuck Brown Day Parking This Way'.
  - Trombone King, Rafael Gerald, and Jeremiah Boulware perform with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2018-01; 199chippy_1963; From left to right Trombone King plays trombone, Jeremiah Boulware plays electric guitar, and Rafael Gerald plays the drums while performing with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Trombone King and Jeremiah Boulware perform with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2018-01; 199chippy_1964; Trombone King plays trombone while performing with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse. Jeremiah Boulware is visible in the background playing electric guitar.
  - Trombone King, Rafael Gerald, and Jeremiah Boulware perform with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2018-01; 199chippy_1965; From left to right Trombone King plays trombone, Jeremiah Boulware plays electric guitar, and Rafael Gerald plays the drums while performing with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Trombone King performs with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse, 2018-01; 199chippy_1966; Trombone King plays trombone while performing with the Experience Band and Show at Ivy City Smokehouse.
  - Protester dances at a Don't Mute D. C. protest, 2018-01; 199chippy_1967; A protester dances at the first Don't Mute D. C. Protest at the corner of 14th and U streets. In the background a person who may be a property owner lobbies a D. C. Metropolitan Police Officer to shut the protest down.
  - Howard Theatre Walk of Fame sign, 2019; 199chippy_1968; A sign for the Howard Theatre Walk of Fame features Chuck Brown, Marvin Gaye, and James Brown. The Howard Theatre is visible in the background.
  - Crowd gathers to watch to a live performance outside of the Reeves Center, 2019; 199chippy_1969; A crowd gathers to listen to a live performance outside of the Reeves Center. Musicians play the drum set, congas, and a cowbell.
  - Fans take pictures of the rapper Wale at a live performance outside of the Reeves Center, 2019; 199chippy_1970; Fans take pictures of the rapper Wale at a live performance outside of the Reeves Center.
  - Crowd gathers to watch to a live performance outside of the Reeves Center, 2019; 199chippy_1971; A crowd gathers to watch to a live performance outside of the Reeves Center. A musician to the left holds a microphone in their right hand and sings. To the right another musicians plays electric guitar.
  - Crowd gathers to watch to a live performance outside of the Reeves Center, 2019; 199chippy_1972; A crowd gathers to watch to a live performance outside of the Reeves Center. A drummer to the left plays timbales while another plays the drum set.
  - Crowd participates in a live performance outside of the Reeves Center, 2019; 199chippy_1973; A crowd participates in a live performance outside of the Reeves Center.
  - Crowd participates in a live performance outside of the Reeves Center, 2019; 199chippy_1974; A crowd participates in a live performance outside of the Reeves Center. In the foreground is a drum set. To the left are congas.
  - Fan dances in the crosswalk at the live outdoor performance at the Reeves Center, 2019; 199chippy_1975; Fan dances in the crosswalk at the live outdoor performance at the Reeves Center.
  - Promotional posters near a crosswalk, 2019; 199chippy_1976; Promotional posters near a crosswalk.
  - Wale attends live outdoor performance at the Reeves Center, 2019; 199chippy_1977; Wale attends live outdoor performance at the Reeves Center.
  - Tear down of the Chuck Brown mural on Sweet Mango in Petworth, 2019; 199chippy_1978; A Hitachi mini-excavator tears down the Chuck Brown mural on the side of Sweet Mango Cafe.
  - Tear down of the Chuck Brown mural on Sweet Mango in Petworth, 2020; 199chippy_1979; A Hitachi mini-excavator tears down the Chuck Brown mural on the side of Sweet Mango Cafe.